1. Using language. Reading and speaking. English jokes.
1. What's that fly doing in my soup?
Swimming, I think.
2. What's that?
It's bean soup.
I don't want to know what it's bean. I want to know what it is now.
3. Waiter, will the pancakes be long?
No, sir. Round.
2. Sherlock Holmes and Dr Watson went camping in a mountainous area.
They were lying in the open air under the stars.
Sherlock Holmes looked up at the stars
and whispered,
Watson, when you look at that beautiful sky,
what do you think of?
Watson replied,
I think of how short life is and how long the universe has lasted.
No, no, Watson, Holmes said.
What do you really think of?
Watson tried again.
I think of how small I am and how vast the sky is.
Try again, Watson, said Holmes. Watson tried a third time.
I think of how cold the universe is and how warm people can be in their beds,
Holmes said.
Watson, you fool, you should be thinking that someone has stolen our tent.
Thank you.